{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"43.2/0.36",
			"answer":"43.2/0.36",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.341/3.1",
			"answer":"0.341/3.1",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.47/4.7",
			"answer":"0.47/4.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"10.6/0.53",
			"answer":"10.6/0.53",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.407/11",
			"answer":"0.407/11",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"86.7/1.7",
			"answer":"86.7/1.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.087/0.87",
			"answer":"0.087/0.87",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"89.1/0.99",
			"answer":"89.1/0.99",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8.14/3.7",
			"answer":"8.14/3.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.316/7.9",
			"answer":"0.316/7.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}